3ABN - Three Angels Broadcasting Network                                     

* #####    [Our TV Networks](https://3abn.org/networks.html)
    
* #####    [Our Radio Networks](https://3abn.org/networks-radio.html)

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective date: January 11, 2021

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://3abn.org website (hereinafter referred to as the "Service") and a live streaming delivery and video-on-demand service of our broadcasts and programming across numerous platforms, including, but not limited to, website streams, YouTube, apps, Roku, Amazon Fire, Apple TV, Verizon FiOs, and others.

3ABN is committed to providing clear and concise information regarding our privacy policies and practices. This Privacy Statement describes how 3ABN collects, uses, and discloses certain personal information in the course of providing streaming and video services. By accessing our streaming services or utilizing our apps or video on demand features, you consent to the information collection and handling practices outlined in this statement. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Statement, the terms used in this Privacy Statement have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://3abn.org.

I. Definitions, Service and Scope
---------------------------------

Definitions
-----------

* **Service**
    
    Our Service for purposes of this Statement consist of the live streaming and corresponding on-demand video services operated by Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc. (“Service”). Our Service covers the full spectrum of 3ABN programming and broadcasting.
    
    3ABN is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of our Users. Furthermore, this Privacy Statement does not apply to the privacy or security practices of any third party.
    
* **Personal Data**
    
    Personal Data means information or likeness of a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
    
* **Usage Data**
    
    Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a live streaming visit).
    
* **Cookies**
    
    Cookies are small files stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
    
* **Data Controller**
    
    Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.
    
    For the purpose of this Privacy Statement, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
    
* **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**
    
    Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.
    
    We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
    
* **Data Subject (or User)**
    
    Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

* * *

II. Information Collection and Use
----------------------------------

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. The personal information varies depending on the Service being utilized, and multiple services may be integrated for a User. The types of personal information collected includes the following:

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally-identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your device’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the specific program or broadcast of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on live streaming or using our on-demand video features, any comments you may provide to our programming, unique device identifiers, and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we hold certain information for recordkeeping purposes. Among other things, cookies enable us to gather information about your activity on our living streaming service for the purpose of improving your experience, establishing secure user accounts, remembering your preferences and settings, and for other similar customization purposes.

Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking technologies are also used such as beacons, tags and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. For example, these technologies can identify popular pages, viewing patterns, click-through, conversion rates, and other information that can be used to improve, monitor, and operate our websites, products, and services.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

For streaming and video, if you create an account, we primarily use cookies to store your name and email, along with a history of the videos you have watched for analytic purposes. We do not collect additional private information beyond that information.

III. Data Use
-------------

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our programming or Services
* To personalize and enhance your experience and or communication
* To provide customer support
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
* To monitor the usage of our Service
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

IV. Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Statement depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it is not overridden by your rights
* For payment processing purposes
* To comply with the law

V. Retention of Data
--------------------

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer periods.

VI. Transfer of Data
--------------------

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Statement followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Statement and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

VII. Disclosure of Data
-----------------------

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

Three Angels Broadcasting Network does not sell personal information collected through these Services.

Security of Data
----------------

The security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We maintain security policies and procedures to handle incidents involving unauthorized access to personal data we process.

Our Statement on "Do Not Track" Signals under the California Online Protection Act (CalOPPA)
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

California residents may avail themselves of rights granted by California laws and regulations.

Your Data Protection Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed about what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
    
* **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
    
* **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
    
* **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
    
* **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”:), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related services or assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. These third parties may have separate and independent privacy statements, terms of use, and related notices or disclosures regarding information handling practices. We cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of independent parties and encourage you to review their practices prior to information disclosure.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Statement. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

* **PayPal**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)
    
* **Authorize.net**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://usa.visa.com/legal/privacy-policy.html](https://usa.visa.com/legal/privacy-policy.html)
    
* **Square**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://squareup.com/us/en/legal/general/privacy-no-account](https://squareup.com/us/en/legal/general/privacy-no-account)
    
* **Stripe**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy)
    
* **EVO Payments**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.evopayments.us/privacy-policy/](https://www.evopayments.us/privacy-policy/)
    
* **Apple Pay through Stripe**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy)
    
* **Google Pay through Stripe**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy)
    
* **Amazon**
    
    Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=GX7NJQ4ZB8MHFRNJ](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=GX7NJQ4ZB8MHFRNJ)

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Statement of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We reserve the right to update our Privacy Statement from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Statement on this page, together with the effective date of change.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Statement.

You are advised to review this Privacy Statement periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Statement are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us:

* By email: mail@3abn.org
* By visiting this page on our website: https://3abn.org/contact.html
* By phone number: 618-627-4651
* By mail: P.O. Box 220 West Frankfort, IL 62896

TRADEMARKS
----------

3ABN, 3ABN Dare to Dream Network, 3ABN Latino Network, 3ABN Latino Radio Network, 3ABN Français Network, 3ABN Proclaim, 3ABN Russia Network, 3ABN Russia Radio Network, 3ABN Radio Network, 3ABN Radio Music Channel, 3ABN Praise Him Music Network, 3ABN International Network, 3ABN Australia Radio Network, 3ABN Kids Network, 3ABN Audio, and the 3ABN logo are registered trademarks of Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc. 3ABN produced program logos are registered trademarks of Three Angels Broadcasting Network, Inc.

* Apple and the Apple logo are trademarks of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries. App Store is a service mark of Apple Inc., registered in the U.S. and other countries.
* Android and Google Play are trademarks of Google, Inc. Verizon FiOS is a registered trademark of Verizon, Inc.
* Facebook and the Facebook logo are trademarks of Facebook Inc.
* Twitter and the Twitter logo are trademarks of Facebook Inc.
* DISH Network logo is a registered trademark of DISH Network, Inc.
* Verizon FiOS is a registered trademark of Verizon, Inc.
